片名：盜火線
Check, charge or cash?
支票、信用卡還是現金？
Cash.
現金
Make it out to...
發票寫…
Jack's Demolition. Tucson.
塔克森市傑克拆卸公司
$788.30.
總數788.30元
Hi, Taking me to breakfast?
和我吃早餐嗎？
I can't. I'm meeting Bosko.
不行 我要去見波斯科
Hei, Vincent.
文森特
Where are my barrettes?
我的髮夾呢？
I saw them on the kitchen table.
我看見在餐桌上
I already checked.
我找過了
Coffee?
咖啡？
No school today?
今天不用上學？
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
爸爸帶我去新大廈然後吃午餐
Try under the sofa cushions.
到沙發墊子下找找
He's already half an hour late.
他遲了半小時了
He's going to show, or stand her up like last time?
他會出現還是像上次那樣爽約？
I'll make coffee.
我煮咖啡
Out of time.
沒時間了
Mom, my barrettes are not on the couch.
我的髮夾不在沙發上
Wear the blue ones.
戴藍色的吧
I don't want to wear the blue ones. They don't match.
我不想戴戴藍色的 顏色不匹配
Did you check in your bathroom? I checked everywhere!
浴室找過沒有？ 找過了
What do you want me to do?
我該怎辦？
Find them!
去找！
Mom, pay attention! All right, sweetie, all right!
媽 留心！好的 親愛的
Daddy's going to be here.
爸快來了
I won't be ready!
我來不及準備
I can't be late. You won't.
我會遲到
I will be late!
我會遲的
Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
若一起找 爸到來前會找到
It's all right, baby. It's all right.
沒事的 寶貝
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them.
我們一起找
Just relax. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
放心 他到來前我們會找到
Give me another refill.
給我添一杯
What's your name?
你叫什麼？
Waingro.
韋恩格羅
You're Michael?
你是邁克爾？
You guys always work together?
你們常一起合作？
All the time.
經常合作
Real tight crew?
合作無間？
Real tight.
是的
If this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
若今次順利 我會考慮再做
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
好的 別再說話 滑頭
How's he doing?
他怎樣？
Hundred percent.
百份之百滿意
Right on schedule.
很準時
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
威尼斯街右轉
We're a mile and a half from you.
我們離你一裡半
Okay.
好
Just crossed over the No. 1 lane, 300 yards from you.
越過行車快線離你三百碼
Get set.
準備
I am.
明白
Here we go.
行動
211!
有劫案！
We're being held up!
我們遇劫
211 alarm. Armored car. There's the call.
裝甲車遇劫 已通知了警方
Three minutes.
有三分鐘
Clear!
離開！
Eighty seconds left!
只剩80秒
Get back! Get back!
退後！
Get back!
Slick, see that shit coming out of their ears? They can't fucking hear you!
滑頭 他耳朵流血 聽不到的
Cool it!
別胡來
I got it.
找到了
Got it.
到手
You had to fuck with me.
你要和我過不去
Want to fuck with me?
和我過不去？
What are you doing? What did he do?
他做什麼？
He was making a move.
他作勢要攻擊
Dumb motherfucker.
狗娘養的
I heard them.
我聽到他們說的
$1.6 million...
160萬
Forty cents on the dollar, $640,000 to you.
分你四成 你可得64萬
Here's $150,000 front money.
這是15萬的預支
Get you the rest in two, three days.
其餘的兩三天后付
Who owned these?
是誰擁有的？
"Malibu Equity and Investments."
馬里布股票及投資公司
Roger Van Zant.
羅傑·範·贊特…
Owns banks in the Caymans...
在開曼群島擁有銀行…
runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
替國外販毒的錢負責投資事務
So?
那麼？
You ripped off his bearer bonds.
你偷了他的債券
He's insured.
他買了保險
That's the point. He collects 100% from the insurance.
他可獲百份之百的保險賠償
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us...
也許他向我們購回債券…
for 60% of their value. Makes 40% on top of the 100%.
以六折價購回 他可以再賺四成
Sell it back to him, that's an extra $320,000 to you.
債券賣給他你可再得32萬
Try it on.
試試看
Kelso called.
凱爾索來電話
About what?
關於什麼事？
A score he's putting out, he wants you to look at.
他有比買賣 想要你看看
I don't need his score. I got my own.
我不需要他的買賣 我自己有
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
據說錢無法追查而且過千萬元
9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
明天九點
What happened?
發生什麼事？
Don't ask.
別問了
Find the ambulance?
找到救護車嗎？
Dumped it four blocks from here.- 22nd Street.
在四條街外被棄  22號街
They torched it. Burned the guns, clothes, everything.
他們放火燒了 槍、衣服、一切都化為灰燼
They were airborne. They taped the last few seconds of the black-and-whites.
記者在半空中拍下幾秒的黑白片
Stolen from Fresno two weeks ago.
車是兩星期前在弗萊斯諾偷的
Yellow pickup truck out of Whittier a day before yesterday.
黃色卡車是前天在惠提爾偷的
You taking this one?
你負責此案？
Or does it stay in Division?
還是由分局調查？
Does this look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
這一宗是便利店劫案嗎？
Robbery-Homicide's taking it.
搶劫及兇殺組接手調查
We got three motorists.
三名司機目擊事發
All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
只看見戴上面罩的人
TV man over there, however, he was closer.
那邊的電視漢子較近現場
Did he ID anybody?
他認出任何人嗎？
He was hiding. He heard it mostly.
他躲起來 聽到大部份對話
What about them?
他們呢？
According to the TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
電視漢說這人在胡言亂語
Smart.
很聰明
Somebody called a guard "Slick."
有人叫護衛做“滑頭”
Now, I figure this guy...
我認為此人…
went for that hold-out piece, ankle holster.
想拿綁在足踝的槍
From here...
由這兒…
bang, bang...
開槍…
bang, bang, bang.
This side.
子彈由這兒穿出
This guy has got what appears to be a double tap-entry wound to the sternum.
這人看來似是胸部中槍
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bone, close range.
從頭的傷勢看似是近距離被殺
Probably executed.
大致如此
It was $1.6 million in bearer bonds.
160萬的債券被盜
They ignored the loose cash.
他們沒拿走現金
'Cause they had no time. They were on a clock.
他們沒時間 時間緊迫
Which means they knew our response time to a 211...
他們知道警方何時會到達
had our air, immobilized it, entered...
聽警方廣播 把車截停 進入…
escaped in under three minutes.
及在三分鐘內逃走
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
這是好地點 有良好逃走路線
Two freeways...
兩條公路…
within a quarter of a mile.
在四分一裡之內
Traffic video camera?
交通錄影
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
可能給弄壞了 但查看一下
You recognize the M. O?
你認出手法嗎？
M. O...
手法…
is that they're good.
是職業劫匪所為
Once it escalated into a murder-one beef for all, after they killed two guards...
他們殺兩警衛犯了一級謀殺罪…
they didn't hesitate.
之後便不再遲疑
Popped guard No. 3 because... what difference does it make?
殺第三名 因為橫豎也是犯罪
Why leave a living witness?
為何留下證人呢？
Drop of a hat,these guys will rock-and-roll.
他們會毫不遲疑 心狠手辣
The shape charge.
定向炸藥
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
顯示劫匪的技術是精通的
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
足以使他們在途中下手
Let's look for recent high-line burglaries that have mystified us.
我們要找偷值錢東西的劫匪
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI. You'll get the phone book.
查“滑頭”這綽號名單可能很長
Do it anyway. Who's moving the bearer bonds?
但還要查 誰賣出債券？
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cuzomano and Torena.
查慣常接贓者 你和我庫左馬努和托爾那
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro.
我要你查戈爾斯坦及阿法羅
Hang in with Forensics.
和鑒證科緊密合作
From the bomb squad, I want the explosive.
向炸彈組查問用的是什麼炸藥
If we're lucky, it's exotic. We can trace the sale.
若是罕見的 可追查發售來源
Get your hand out of that man's pocket.
你別伸手進那人的口袋
Anyone want some pie?
有誰要吃餡餅？
Gotta go to the john.
我要上廁所
I had to get it on. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他作勢攻擊我要先下手為強
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
他那份在車上 我們的均分了…
to make up for his full end...
以便全數給他…
'cause I want to pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
因我想立即分給和打發這雜種
Hold it!
等一等
Where's the rest?
其餘的錢呢？
We're late. You look too good to go out.
時候不早了 你打扮得很漂亮
I'll just jump you right here.
我想在這兒和你做愛
Where is it? Squared the bookies, baby.
錢呢？  還賭債了
There's more in a couple of days, so don't sweat it. We're late.
幾天後還會有錢 放心吧
Come on.
少胡說
You gotta be kidding me.
你定是說笑
Honey...
親愛的…
it ain't worth the risks you take for $8,000. Like in "Risk versus reward."
為區區八千元值得冒這個險嗎？
Let's go.
走吧
Get your coat.
拿你的外衣
There's no point talking. You're just a child growing older.
無謂再說 你心智還沒成熟
What does that mean?
什麼意思？
We're not making forward progress like real grown-up adults living our lives...
我們不像成年人那樣有進步…
because I married a gambling junkie.
因為我嫁給一個賭徒
Get in the fucking car.
上車吧
What am I doing in here?
我怎可以這樣下去的？
You're not!
你不用！
Leave the bank book and the car keys...
你離開這裡時留下…
in the kitchen on your way out!
銀行存摺和車匙
Are we going? Keep that crap. Dominick comes with me.
你留著吧 我帶多明尼克走
Don't even think about...
你別妄想…
Tell me Albert Torena called back.
阿爾伯特·托爾那回電話了
Albert Torena call Vincent?
阿爾伯特·托爾那有給文森特電話嗎？
No.
沒有
Report came in.
有報告
The explosive was Dy-Ex, used in demolition.
炸藥是拆毀用的…
You can pick it up in Nevada...
可在內華達…
Arizona, New Mexico.
亞利桑那、新墨西哥州買到
Too common to trace a sale.
太普通難以追查來源
That's wonderful.
那太好了
You all right?
你沒事吧？
What happened? Where have you been?
怎麼了？你去了哪兒？
Work.
工作
Lauren's dad show up?
勞倫的父親有來嗎？
Didn't call...
沒來電話…
didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
沒出現 我們一直等到十點半
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with this kid?
這人知道他女兒是怎樣的嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道
Fucking jerk.
該死的混蛋
Is she okay?
她沒事吧？
She's been in her room all day.
她整天在房內
So, no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
她有事 我也不開心
I made dinner...
我弄了晚餐…
for us, four hours ago.
四小時前為我們煮了
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us...
我設法替我們保持一貫的情緒
you withdraw.
你退卻了
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk...
在威尼斯大道旁邊…
off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
躺著三名死者 賈斯汀
I'm sorry...
對不起…
if the goddamn...
若那可惡的…
chicken...
雞肉…
got overcooked.
給煮過了頭
Coffee, sir?
要咖啡嗎？
Please.
好的
Will you pass the cream?
請把奶遞給我
Thanks.
謝謝
What'd you get?
你買了什麼？
What?
什麼？
What are you reading?
你看什麼書？
Book about metals.
關於金屬的書
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
鈦的應力折斷
What kind of work do you do?
你做什麼的？
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
你為何對我看什麼書感興趣？
I've seen you in the store.
我在店中看見你
What store?
什麼店？
Hennessey and Ingalls. I work there.
我在書店工作
If you don't want to talk to me, it's okay.
若你不想交談 好的
I'm sorry I bothered you.
抱歉打擾了你
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我不想無禮 只是認不出你
I work in metals. I'm a salesman.
我是推銷員 專營金屬的
My name's Neil.
我叫尼爾
I'm Eady.
我叫伊荻
You like working there?
你喜歡在書店工作？
Sure.
是的
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
我買書有折扣也有我行內的書
What area?
是哪一行業？
Graphic design.
平面設計
I do letterheads and logotypes at night and...
晚上設計信紙及商標…
the store's a day job until I get enough going.
白天在書店工作直至能藉此謀生
Who do you do that for?
你為誰設計呢？
A restaurant.
餐廳
I did their menus, and...
我設計他們的餐牌 以及…
a small record label.
為小唱片公司設計
CDs.
鐳射唱片封套
I've done two so far.
目前已設計了兩張
You go to school for that?
你上學校受訓嗎？
Yeah.
是的
I went to Parsons.
我念過帕森斯學校
Where's that?
在哪兒？
New York City.
紐約市
How long you been here?
你在這兒住了多久？
About a year.
約一年
Like it?
喜歡這兒嗎？
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
不算喜歡 我為工作才來這兒
Live in this neighborhood?
你住在附近？
No, I live kind of above Sunset Plaza.
不 我住在日落廣場上面山上
It's a little house I rent.
租住一所小房子
And it's kind of rundown, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
頗為破舊 但景觀極佳
What about you?
你呢？
I live up here.
我住在這兒
That's very funny.
很有趣
Where's your family from originally?
你的家人原本從哪兒來？
They're Scotch-Irish.
蘇格蘭及愛爾蘭
They emigrated to Appalachia...
他們移居美國東南部
in the late 1700s.
在1700年末期
Where are you from?
你從哪兒來？
The Bay area.
海灣地區
Your folks there?
家人在那兒？
My mother died a long time ago, and my father...
母親很久前死了 我父親…
I don't know where he is.
我不知他在哪兒
Got a brother somewhere.
我有個兄弟
You have a tight family. I can tell.
你的家人關係很緊密吧？
Right?
是嗎？
You're right.
你說的對
City of lights.
燈火通明的城市
In Fiji, they have...
在菲濟 有一種…
iridescent algae that come out once a year in the water.
會發光的海藻每年浮出水面一次
That's what it looks like out there.
這城市的燈正是如此
You been there?
你到過菲濟？
No, I'm going there someday.
沒有 我終有一天會去
You travel a lot?
你常旅遊？
Yeah.
是的
Traveling make you lonely?
旅遊使你寂寞？
I'm alone. I am not...
我一個人 可我並不…
lonely.
寂寞
You?
你呢？
Real lonely.
很寂寞
Albert!
阿爾伯特！
Shit!
糟了！
What you doing here? You crazy? This ain't Disneyland.
你為何來這兒？你瘋了嗎？
You were supposed to get back to me.
你該覆我電話的
Where the fuck you been?
你去了哪兒？
I couldn't break free.
我無法脫身
Let's violate his ass right now.
我們侵犯他的民權吧
I do for you...
我幫忙你…
you don't do for me, is that it?
你卻不幫我 是這樣嗎？
Vincent, man. I swear, I was out all night. I'm hitting like a Flamingo matador.
我整晚外出 為你刺探消息
That's got nothing to do with me.
此事和我無關
I'm cutting it smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you. I'm a dancer.
我順利為你找到線索 我很棒
You bullshit.
你胡說
I paged your ass all day. I hate fucking paging.
我傳呼你一整天 我討厭這樣做
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
你又成了癮君子？注射毒品？
Where's your empathy? It's a substance abuse problem.
體諒下 我有濫用藥物的問題
Empathy was yesterday. Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
我昨天同情你 你他媽今天浪費我時間
You fall in love?
你戀愛了？
Did you fall in love...
你是否戀愛…
and went off somewhere?
還是到別處去了？
Tell me that, I'll settle for it.
我會接受這解釋
Give me all you got!
把消息告訴我！
I swear, my brother Richard's going to talk to you.
我發誓我哥哥理查會跟你說
I heard Richard?
你是說理查嗎？
He's going to talk to you.
他會和你說的
He's gonna meet you tonight.
他今晚會見你
He's not here, is he?
他不在這兒？
No, he'll meet you tonight.
不 他會見你的
What happened to now?
現在不行嗎？
I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
我懇求他因為我知道你今早會來
Bullshit.
胡說
I swear. He said no...
我發誓 他說不…
'cause he in Phoenix.
…因為他在鳳凰城
By the time I get to Phoenix
我到了鳳凰城後…
He'll be rising
他剛好起程…
He'll probably leave a note
他留下字條…
Right on the door
貼在門上
Tonight's the best I can do for you.
我只能令他今晚見你
He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado.
今晚在艾華瓦度街BJ夜總會
At 2:00 a.m.
淩晨二點
Be there.
你去吧
You be there, too.
你也要到
I can't be there, man. I got things to do.
不行 我有事要辦
I got things to do, I got places to be.
我有事辦 要到別處
Be there.
你要去
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
別他媽浪費我時間
What is it?
是什麼買賣？
It's a bank.
是銀行
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
星期四會存錢以便分發各分行…
to cover Friday payroll checks.
應付星期五支付薪金的支票
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
因此星期四分行總會放滿現鈔
On the prowl or strong?
在途中下手還是搶銀行？
Strong. Through the door.
由正門進入
How many guys?
有多少人？
About four, or three, plus a driver. You walk in, knock 'em over, walk out.
連司機四人 走進銀行得手便走
You want $100,000 in advance against a ten-percent cut for that?
你要先拿十萬事成後分一成？
Sounds like a cowboy score.
聽起來像西部牛仔搶銀行
They hit the hold-up alarms, I gotta get out before the cops show.
他們按動警鐘我得在之前離去
They hit three hold-up alarm systems.
他們可按動三個遇劫警鐘
Two Telco and a cellular.
兩個一般警鐘和一個蜂窩式的…
But the signals aren't going anywhere because...
但訊號無法傳送出去 因為…
the night before...
之前一晚…
you cut in...
你潛進銀行…
and trick out the alarm system computer...
破壞警報系統的電腦…
to turn itself...
使電腦…
and the video recorders off...
及錄影裝置…
20 minutes before you enter.
在你下手前20分鐘關掉
Architectural, electrical plans?
你有建築及電子藍圖？
I got that.
我有
I got the boards already built. They go right into the CPU.
我建造電腦板 直駁中央處理器
What's the estimate?
估計可有多少錢？
$12.1, $12.2 million.
1210萬到1220萬
You're on.
我會參加
Congratulations.
恭喜
Let me give you a little idea of where my estimates come from.
我告訴你如何估計會有這筆錢
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
沒人知道貨是你的
My way, you get 100% from the insurance company...
我讓你得保險全數賠償
take the bonds back from us...
把債券回購
at 60 cents on the dollar and make yourself another 40%.
以六成的價格 可多賺40%
The operation doesn't skip a beat. We all make out.
行動全無損失我們均可賺大錢
Sure, you got a deal.
我同意
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets upset.
好 若大家不喜歡便沒有得益
You have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
要你的人給我電話 安排會面
Yeah, okay.
好的
Nice talking to you.
很高興和你通電話
You gonna deal with these guys?
你和他們交易？
Word's on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
江湖上可接受我偷自己的東西嗎
I'm going to kill these sons of bitches.
我會殺了這班渾蛋
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Island's Offshore.
讓哈利把加那利群島的表格拿給我
That's not really an estimate. Those are exact figures.
這些不是估計 是實在數字
I have a printout of the bank's cash flow for the past two months.
我印出銀行過去兩月的現金帳
How'd you get this information?
資料怎得來的？
Just comes to you.
送上門的
This stuff just flies through the air.
資料到處都是
It's just beamed out all over the place. You just have to grab it.
到處傳送 只需加以掌握便行
I know how to grab it.
我懂得掌握
Okay, here we go.
這是我們要的
$13.9 million.
1390萬
I bought it. Good.
我同意了 很好
What did I tell you?
我沒說錯吧
Here.
拿著
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
同意了 聯絡範·贊特和收錢吧
How is he?
他怎樣？
He's a businessman.
他是生意人
Chris is at my place.
克裡斯在我家中
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Husband-and-wife stuff.
夫妻的爭吵
I'll let him sleep it off.
我讓他睡醒再說
What happened to you?
你怎麼了？
When will you get some furniture?
你何時買傢俱？
When I get around to it.
我有時間便買
Charlene's gonna leave me.
沙琳要離開我
Why?
為什麼？
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我沒錢好好供養她
With everything we've been doing?
我們做買賣還不夠錢？
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
賭場及賭球賽使我身無分文
When you gonna get an old lady?
你何時會結婚？
When I get around to it.
有時間再說
You got something else on the side?
你有外遇嗎？
Nothing regular.
沒固定的
She got something else on the side?
她有外遇嗎？
No. You sure?
沒有 你肯定嗎？
Yeah, I'm sure.
肯定
I don't know what you're doing.
我不知你做什麼
As Jimmy said, "You want to be making moves on the street?
如吉米說 如果你要成為罪犯？
"Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
要無牽掛 生活中不能有…
"that you can't walk out on in 30 seconds if you spot the heat around the corner."
任何牽掛 風聲緊時可一走了之
Remember that?
記得嗎？
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
她是我一生中最重要的
We take the delivery of cash from Van Zant...
我們從範·贊特那兒拿到錢…
then I drop a deposit on Kelso for this bank.
然後為搶銀行的事存錢給凱爾索
Bank? What bank?
什麼銀行？
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
這白金的事如何？快成事了
That goes, too. Then the bank.
那也會進行 然後再搶銀行
Want some breakfast?
要吃早餐嗎？
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
Yeah, sugar.
沒事
For real.
是真的
I'll do good.
我會好好的做
I'll see you later.
再見
You Solenko?
你是索倫戈？
I'm Don Breedan.
唐納德·布裡丹
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come here, see if you had a job for me.
假釋官告訴我你會有工作給我
You're familiar with this kind of operation?
你對這兒的工作熟悉嗎？
I'm a great grill man.
我燒烤很出色的
Good. Good for you.
好
You'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher, bus tables and empty the garbage.
你洗抹廁所 洗碗碟收拾桌子
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
你煩我 我會舉報你藏毒酗酒或偷竊
I'll violate you back fast.
舉報你違反假釋條例
Twenty-five percent of your take-home kicks back to me.
你給我薪金的25%作回傭
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out. Change in the back.
是規矩 問假釋官吧 後面更衣
What are you waiting for?
你還等什麼？
Malibu Equity and Investments.
馬里布股票及投資
Roger Van Zant.
羅傑·範·贊特
Please hold.
請等一等
This is Roger Van Zant.
我是羅傑·範·贊特
I'm supposed to collect something.
我有一些東西
Someone will call you back from another line.
會有人給你電話
818-133-6089.
I got a package for you. There's a drive-in on Centinela. 2:30 tomorrow.
明午二點半露天影院見
Just send one man, alone.
只派一人單獨前來
Who was that guy? Nobody.
那人是誰？ 無名小卒
I gotta know who he is! Who is he?
我要知道他是誰
He's nobody, Neil.
他是無名小卒
He's a legit liquor wholesaler from Las Vegas. Alan Marciano.
是賭城合法酒類推銷員阿蘭·馬西阿諾
Chris will make up.
克裡斯會和你和解
It's too late! I'm sick of it! Shut up!
太遲了！我討厭他！ 閉嘴
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot.
你再給克裡斯一次機會 若他犯錯…
After that, he fucks up, then I will  finance setting you up myself ...on my own, anywhere you want.
我會資助你找地方住 哪兒都行
Dominick will go with you.
多明尼克會跟著你
And my word counts. But right now...
我言出必行的 但現在…
you will give him the chance.
你會給他機會
Clean up. Go home.
清洗一下 回家去
Clean up. Go home!
清洗一下 回家！
Give me all your money.
交出你的錢
You'll get smoked with that shit.
你會因此而沒命的
Won't be you.
殺我的不會是你
He's coming in alone. Send him through.
他一個人來
Vincent, hey, man.
文森特
This is my brother, Richard. Vincent.
這是我哥哥理查 文森特
It's all right.
沒關係
What have you got for me?
你有何消息告訴我？
Before we even get into that, there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach.
談正題前 沙灘附近有人偷車
Now, in the back of a trim shop...
在汽車裝飾店後
if somebody wants to pay a little visit this weekend...
若週末有人前去那兒…
they might find two Turbos and a 911 Slope.
會找到一輛名貴跑車
You're looking to rid yourself of your competition?
你想讓我幫你擺脫你的對手？
I'm a good citizen.
我是個好市民
I'm Donald Duck.
我才不信
You got something to tell me?
你有事要告訴我？
Check this out, cuz.
你聽著 朋友
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
我怎知若我說出你所想知的事…
that you're gonna do what the fuck I need to get done.
你會做我所想做的事
Richard. Hanna is straight up.  We do business all the time.
漢娜很可靠的 我們做過很多交易
I ain't your cuz, you rat motherfucker.
雜種 我不是你的朋友
And you know because I say so...
你知道我說得出做得到…
after I hear what the fuck you got to tell me!
但我要先聽你有什麼話要說
Fuck you.
操你媽
You understand?
明白嗎？
I can get killed for telling you this.
我說出來會沒命的
You can get killed walking your doggie!
你溜狗時也會沒命
All right, man...
好吧
there was a cat I was locked up with.
我和這人在獄中…
Did a couple of two, three years. He got out. I ran into him.
服刑兩三年 他出獄後我碰上他
And so?
那又怎樣？
He's a big fiend for action.
他是坐言起行的人
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing, but...
若他不說我便不會去想 可是…
he goes on and on, telling me how he ain't done nothing...
他不斷的對我說他什麼也沒做…
and nothing's been going on, and all this bullshit.
而且也沒事發生 等等屁話
Right then and there I know...
那時我便知道…
this cat's got something going down.
這人參與了不法行為
Pretty fucking great.
而且是大案
Albert, what's wrong with you?
阿爾伯特 你怎麼回事了？
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你要我來這裡 浪費我的時間
You saw a guy on the street who's an ex-con?
你見過坐過牢的人？
That's right.
是的
Well, I am...
那麼我…
over-fucking-whelmed.
很喜出望外
What do you want for that, a junior G-man badge?
你想為此拿勳章嗎？
You gonna make the call on them Porsches?
你會查跑車的事嗎？
Is he kidding me?
他是說笑嗎？
I'm telling you:
我告訴你
This Slick is no joke.
滑頭不是說笑的
He's double time.
他為人緊張
Say what?
你說什麼？
"Slick." What does that mean?
滑頭 是什麼意思？
That's what he calls people: "Slick."
他常叫別人為“滑頭”
Tell me about him.
把他的事告訴我
About 6 feet tall...
他約六尺高…
lots of jailhouse tats.
有許多監獄的紋身
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
這兒刺有一頭大孔雀
What's his name?
他叫什麼名字？
Cheritto.
克裡托
Michael Cheritto.
邁克爾·克裡托
Thirty-three busts since 1976.
自1976年起被捕33次
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
11次持械行劫 3次給定罪
Two out of a three-to-five year beef in Attica.
判刑3至5年在紐約服刑兩年
Three years in Marion.
中西部服刑3年
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back to involuntary manslaughter.
因誤殺罪在福爾索姆監獄服刑5年
Jacket's two inches thick.
他的案底達兩英寸厚
Who do I have there now?
現在還有誰有聽？
Drucker and me. And Schwartz. Tell SIS...
德魯克、我和施瓦茲
I want full surveillance. That's 24 hours. Round the clock, day and night.
我要24小時監視他
We never close. Open every day.
不斷監視跟蹤他
Bug the car, the house, the work.
監聽他的汽車和房子
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant...
一舉一動和誰人一起也拍照
I want pictures of who he moves and sits with. Then run makes on them.They got jackets, trail them.
調查他們 若有案底便跟蹤他們
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
我要明天便執行
Put your hands where I can see them.
把手放在我看到的地方
I tell you what to do.
我會告訴你怎麼樣做
I tell you how to do it.
以及該怎麼做
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
現在 只用你的右手只准右手…
take the package and throw it in here.
把包裹拿出來 扔過來
Behind you.
你後面有人
On the right.
在你右邊
Roger Van Zant.
羅傑·範·贊特
Who's this?
你是誰？
You know who this is.
你知道我是誰
Yes, I do.
我知道
I sent a guy to deliver the package.
我派人送包裹
He didn't call. Is everything okay?
他沒來電話 一切妥當吧
I tell you what, forget the money.
我告訴你 忘記那筆錢
What?
什麼？
Forget the money.
忘記那筆錢
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, "Forget the money"?
數目不少 你做什麼？你到底什麼意思
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone.
我對著話筒自說自話
I don't understand.
我不明白
'Cause there is a dead man on the other end of this line.
因為電話的另一端是個死人
Do you like it?
你喜歡嗎？
Look at my ring.
看我的戒指
Did you know?
你知道的？
You are insane.
你瘋了
Do you like it?
喜歡嗎？
It's beautiful. It's good.
很漂亮
Don't ask him where he got it.
別問他哪兒得來的
What do you want to be when you grow up?
你長大後想做什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道
Just like me.
像我一樣
I don't know either.
我也不知道
Hello?
你好
It's me.
是我
I was wondering if you'd call.
我在想你是否會來電話
I've been busy.
我很忙
Can I see you?
我可以見你嗎？
I was afraid that was just...
我害怕那只是…
the one night.
一夜情
Not for me, it wasn't.
對我來說不是
Yeah, me neither.
我也不是
Can I fall by?
我可以來嗎？
Yeah.
好的
I'll see you in a little bit.
一會兒見
Goddamn convention.
可惡的會議
Which one's Slick? The wide one.
哪個是滑頭？ 魁悟的那個
We got two transmitters.
有兩個監視器
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
分別在防火板及輪內
Here we are.
是我們的車
Did you say goodnight to Neil?
跟尼爾道別了嗎？
The blond is Chris Shiherlis.
金髮的是克裡斯·謝裡斯
SIS has got a revolving tail and hung a wire on the house phone.
特別調查組派人跟他偷聽電話
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
克裡托把車三次駛過貴重金屬庫
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
白金、銀和一些金條
Sammy and I think that will be their next score.
薩米和我認為是他們下一目標
Who's the loner?
那獨行者是誰？
First time we've seen him.
我們第一次見他
We're not on him yet.
還沒開始跟蹤他
Get on it.
立即開始吧
Ok.
好了
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take next...
他們下次做案得手走出大門時…
they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
定會大感驚愕
Baby, time to go.
我要走了
Showed you a good time, didn't I?
我令你很開心吧
You fly.
你很棒
You're cool.
你不錯
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
你騙我 我看得出別人騙我
I ain't lying.
我沒說謊
You're a hot dog.
你很勇猛
A regular rodeo rider.
是出色的騎士
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
是我試過最精彩的性行為
Now, I got to get my ass street-side, sugar.
我現在得回到街上去
You don't have a truth-telling style.
你可沒有說實話
What are you talking about?
你說什麼？
You don't know what this is.
你不知道是怎麼回事？
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
是死神來探望你
Where have you been?
你去了哪兒？
SHU at Pelican Bay.
塘鵝彎的特別收容所
Folsom, B-wing.
以及福爾索姆監獄B座
I am a cowboy...
我是一個牛仔…
looking for anything heavy.
想做大買賣的人
Billy said to come see you.
比利說來找你
That is why I am here.
因此我來了
Why don't you call this guy?
你給這人打電話吧
This guy's always putting guys on.
他經常招人入夥
Thank you.
謝謝
What's your funny.
有什麼可笑的
It's really dog.
它真是條狗
You're perfect for each other.
你們真是天生一對
I knew a guy in grade school.
我念小學時認識一人
His name was Raoul... whatever.
他叫羅爾…什麼的
You could take his fingers and fold them over each other.
他可把手指彼此屈折起來
He'd turn his eyelids inside out...
他可把眼皮向外翻…
I can't keep my hands off you.  That's the truth.
我禁不住對你上下其手 是真的
That's what's so wonderful about you in that...
你吸引的地方在於你那…
bestial sort of way.
獸性的方式
Woman.
女人
This better be earth-shattering.
這最好是轟動的大事
This is to Raoul.
為羅爾乾杯
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
我是漢娜·文森特
Here's how we found her.
發現她時是這樣的
How old?
她有多大？
Sixteen, seventeen. Been here about six hours.
十六七歲 在此約六小時
How'd she die?
她怎麼死的？
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
頭部給重擊 大腦血腫
Who's that?
那是誰？
Mother and siblings.
死者母親及兄弟
Why are they here? It's fucked up.
他們為何到來？
Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
酒店內有人認識死者通知家人
Let's go.
讓我看看
Nice.
不錯
My intuition says the DNA check on the semen will show it's the same guy...
直覺告訴我化驗精液是同一人…
so it's a series and ending up in your court.
是連環謀殺案 要由你著手調查
Sheriff's getting anywhere?
警長有頭緒嗎？
Not yet.
還沒有
Get off of me!
放開我！
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Where is she?
她在哪兒？
Easy, easy, easy.
冷靜！
Please, come on.
別這樣
It's okay.
沒事的
Where is my baby? Where is she?
我的女兒呢？
I need to know what happened.
我要知道是怎麼回事
I guess the earth shattered.
我猜是很轟動吧
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
你為何不讓波斯科送你回家？
I didn't want to ruin their night, too.
我不想掃他們的興
What was it?
有什麼事？
You don't want to know.
你不想知道的
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look on your face.
我想知道你為何扳起臉孔
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go.
我不能透露 你是知道的
You never told me I'd be excluded.
你從沒告訴我 我會被排除在外
I told you when we hooked up...
我告訴你我們在一起時…
that you'd have to share me...
你要和我分享…
with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
世上所有的醜行及醜惡的人
And I bought into that sharing...
我同意接受分享…
because I love you.
因為我愛你
I love you fat, bald, money, no money, driving a bus.
你發胖、禿頭、沒錢 開巴士
I don't care.
我不在乎
But you have got to be present like a normal guy.
但你定要存在
That's sharing. This is not sharing, this is leftovers.
那是分享 這不是分享是殘餘的
What I should do is come home and say:
我應該做的是回家然後說：
"Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
你知道嗎？我今天走進一房子…
"where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
這癮君子用微波爐煮熟了孩子…
"because he was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
因他哭的太吵鬧 我和你分享吧
"Come on, let's share that and in sharing it...
讓我們分享此事 而在分享時…
"we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit."
我們會宣洩一切可怕的事件
Right?
對嗎？
Wrong.
錯
You know why?
你知道為什麼嗎？
'Cause you prefer the normal routine.
你喜歡正常的做法
We fuck and you don't speak.
我們做愛 你不說話
'Cause I got to hold on to my angst.
我得保持我的痛苦
I preserve it...
我保存它…
because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
因為我需要藉此提高警覺
Where I gotta be.
我要這樣做
You don't live with me.
你不是和我同住
You live among the remains of dead people.
你和死者的殘骸同住
You read the terrain.
你篩選碎片在地勢找線索
You search for signs of passing...
你找尋死亡的跡象…
for the scent of your prey...
找獵物的氣味…
and then you hunt them down.
然後追捕他們
That's the only thing you're committed to.
這是你唯一投入的事
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
其餘的是你留下的爛攤子
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
我不明白為何不能離開你
Let's go, baby.
走吧
I met the manager.
我見過經理
Is that the boss?
那是老闆嗎？
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
我為他每天所做的事而坐牢
Can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你可忍受直至找到新工作嗎？
Can you do that?
你可以嗎？
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
更難忍受的我也捱過
Why're you hanging with me?
你為何和我一起
Because I'm proud of you.
因為你令我感到驕傲
You're proud of me?
你以我為榮？
Why the hell are you proud of me?
為什麼？
Come on home.
回家吧
What were you doing there?
你在那做什麼？
I was skiing.
我滑雪
I was trying to ski.
我想滑雪
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
那兒的人會這樣做 去滑雪…
and you meet people.
可結識別人
You try to have a good time.
你想開心一下
Did you have a good time? No.
你開心嗎？不
Why not?
為什麼？
I'm not good at meeting people.
我不擅交際
You met me.
你認識了我
That happened without my thinking about it.
我沒加細想事情便發生了
Which is why I probably...
可能是因為這樣…
No, it's because you are fine.
不 是因為你是好的女子
Take off with me for a while.
和我到外地去
Where?
去哪？
New Zealand.
紐西蘭
When?
何時？
I have to go separate. You can meet me there.
我不能和你去 我們在那會和
But my job...
但我的工作
I got money. You don't need money.
我有錢 你不用工作
You could set up a studio and work there.
你可在那兒開設計公司
I don't know.
我不知道
What's there to know?
還要知道什麼？
Are you married?
你結了婚沒有？
What?
什麼？
The last thing I am is married.
我才沒有結婚
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way.
我的生活正在走下坡
Then, all of a sudden...
可是 突然…
someone like you comes along.
出現了你這樣的人
You don't know me.
你不瞭解我
I know enough.
我已瞭解
Come with me.
跟我走
What's wrong?
有何不妥？
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
沒什麼 一切妥當 你會去嗎？
Yeah.
好
Good.
Hi, sweetie.
親愛的
You forget your mom was picking you up?
你忘記媽媽會接你嗎？
No.
不是
So, what's going on?
怎麼回事？
I felt like being alone.
我想獨自一人
Come on, I'll drive you home.
我送你回家
What's happening?
有何動靜？
Sir.
長官
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
警長想知道有何動靜
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
沒動靜 不要用無線電
Technique.
好技術
Open Sesame. Right there.
芝麻開門
There he is.
就是他
We walk!
我們走吧
I'm there.
我快完事了
We walk! Now!
走吧
He's heard it.
他聽到了
Heads up.
他們來了
One's coming out. Hold it, Captain.
有一個出來了 等一等
Vincent, he's not carrying anything.
文森特 他沒帶走任何東西
I see.
我看見
Here we go. Not till my boss says so.
行動 由我上司批准
Both of them are not carrying anything.
他們沒拿東西
Let them go. What do you mean?
讓他們走 什麼?
We can take them...
我們可以拘捕他們
On what?
控以何罪？
They didn't steal anything yet.
他們什麼也沒偷
It gets knocked back to a misdemeanor, they do six months and they're out.
行為不檢他們坐牢半年便出獄
No fucking way.
不行
I'm not taking the heat from my boss. They are not walking.
我會受我頭的批評 他們不能走
That's exactly what they'll do. They'll walk. This is my operation.
他們必須走 今次行動由我指揮
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
我的戰略指揮淩駕你的職級
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck!
讓他們走 你必須讓他們走 見鬼
Back to work.
回去工作
LAPD, the G, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
洛杉磯員警？他媽的員警怎麼會在那兒？
Maybe it's the score they were onto. The place, not us.
他們可能知道那兒被劫 但不知道是我們
Because it's been hit a couple of times.
因為那兒以前曾遇劫
Assume they got our phones, our houses, that they got us right here, right now...
假設他們知道我們的電話住所
as we sit. Everything. Assume it all.
假設一切
How will we buy the bank package?
我們如何付搶銀行的上期？
I'll front that.
我先墊付吧
What about Van Zant?
範·贊特呢？
With the heat we got, you want to play World War II on the streets with Van Zant?
警方追查我們你想和他開戰嗎？
No, I want my 750.
不 我想拿75萬
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luxury.
我比你更想殺了範·贊特
Our problem is to take the bank, or split right now.
問題是我們搶銀行還是離去
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
不要回家收拾東西
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are  gone on our separate ways. That's it.
30秒後我們會各走各路
The bank is worth the risk.
值得冒險搶銀行
I need it, brother.
我需要錢
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
我認為我們該留下來搶銀行
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever.
你做什麼我也跟著
Whatever. Not on this one.
但這次不行
On this one, you're on your own.
你要自行決定
You figure this is the best thing to do?
這是最好的做法嗎？
This is the best thing to do?
是最好的做法嗎？
I've got plans, I'm going away after, so the reward is worth the stretch.
事後我有打算值得為這筆錢坐牢
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
但伊萊恩很照顧你 你有許多錢
You got T-bonds, real estate.
你有物業 若我是你…
If I were you, I would be smart and cut loose of this.
便不參與今次行動
For me...
對我來說…
the action is the juice.
行動使生活更刺激
I'm in.
我參加
Yeah, sure.
我會
Let's go.
動手吧
Fuck them, let's do it.
去他們的 行動吧
Let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
我們有許多事要做
Will. I will.
可以的話我會的
Tim, I gotta call you back.
蒂姆 我給你電話吧
Can I help you?  Are you Alan Marciano?
我能幫你什麼 你是阿蘭·馬西阿諾嗎？
Who the fuck are you?
你他媽是誰？
Who am I?
我是誰？
Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, LAPD.
洛杉磯警察局的漢娜·文森特探長
LA? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
這兒是賭場 不是你權力範圍
Do you know who you're pushing around? I know people here.
你知道你他媽的在惹惱誰嗎？我認識人
Las Vegas PD takes you into custody.
我可要賭城警方拘押你
You are extradited to Newark on a warrant for smuggling cigarettes...
你會因從北卡羅來納走私香煙…
up from North Carolina three years ago...
而給引渡回紐華克…
or you go to work for us.
或是你可以和我們合作
Cut and dried.
簡單明快
That is it.
就是這樣
Shit.
媽的
Charlene Shiherlis.
沙琳·謝裡斯
Who?
誰？
What are you, a fucking owl?
你是什麼 他媽的貓頭鷹嗎？
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day last week.
和你在電話中打情罵俏的女子
You can't tie me to her.
你不能把她和我扯上了
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jackoff.
你肯定會回去新澤西的 笨蛋
Why did I get mixed up with her?
我為何會勾搭上她？
Because she's got a great ass!
因為她的屁股動人
And you got your head all the way up it.
你不知自己在做什麼
Jesus.
天啊
Ferocious, aren't I?
我很凶 是嗎？
When I think of asses...
當我想起屁股…
a woman's ass...
女人的屁股…
something comes out of me.
便想起一些東西
So?
那麼？
So, no big thing.
不要你說太多
All I want...
我只想…
is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
知道她丈夫和他那夥人
You'll work with Sgt. Drucker.
你會和德魯克合作
San Clemente Road and Hermosa...
聖克萊門特路和赫莫薩街
that's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
我們在那兒穿過欄柵
Right.
對
The security systems around here are a joke.
保安系統不堪一擊
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's escape route No. 1.
逃走路線一是聖文森特·湯瑪斯橋
No. 2:
路線二…
Over here. Anaheim to the 110.
是阿納海姆公路往110公路
Good.
好
You got it?
明白嗎？
Good. Let's go.
好的 走吧
They were looking back...
他們回頭望向…
in this direction.
這方向
A container facility?
集裝箱？
What? Cartage theft?
什麼？集裝箱？
Too visible. Too lowball for them.
太明顯了 對他們來說得益太少了
There's an oil refinery and a scrap yard.
有煉油廠、廢車場
Refinery only pays by check.
煉油廠發薪用支票
No cash around.
沒有現金
Same for the scrap yard.
廢車場也一樣
Stealing hubcaps?
偷車輪蓋？
A refinery and a scrap yard.
煉油廠和廢車場？
What the hell is going on?
是怎麼回事？
That's what we are trying to figure out.
我們正想知道
We thought we had it.
我們以為知道了
Thought we had it.
沒弄明白
I got an idea...
我知道…
on what they were looking at.
他們在看些什麼
Want to know what they're looking at?
你們要知道嗎？
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
這人真了不起 他真行
This crew is good.
這夥人很棒
Know what they're looking at?
想知道他們看什麼嗎？
What?
是什麼？
Us.
我們
The LAPD.
洛杉磯警察局
The police department.
辦案員警
We just got made.
我們給人認出來了
Yeah!
耶
Okay!
好吧
Okay, motherfucker!
好吧 雜種
Kelso come through?
凱爾索交出了嗎？
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
是的 藍圖很詳盡
Name is Hanna.
那人姓漢娜
First name, Vincent.
名文森特
I smeared this sergeant five yards.
我用五百元賄賂這警員
Hanna's all over you.
漢娜監視你一舉一動
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house. Shiherlis's.
監視所有的車、邁克爾及謝裡斯的家
Not yours. They've been losing you at night.
沒監視你 不知你晚上在哪兒
He's a hot dog.
他很積極
Graduate school. Marine Corps.
他畢業後加入海軍陸戰隊
Lieutenant in Robbery-Homicide.
是劫案及兇殺組探長
He's taken down some heavy crews. He blew away Frankie in Chicago.
拘捕不少人在芝加哥殺了弗蘭克
He was a fucking maniac.
文森特是個瘋子
He was working Narcotics before that.
他之前在毒品科工作
Divorced twice. Current wife's Justine.
離婚兩次 目前的太太叫賈斯汀
He's why the extra heat.
是他鼓動嚴密監視的
The vice sergeant...
罪案科警官…
says Hanna likes you...
說漢娜喜歡你…
thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, that sharp.
認為你是明星 行事很有技巧
Look how sharp this guy is to figure that.
他能想到這樣看他有多聰明
Funny as a heart attack.
這傢伙很有意思
Three marriages? Do you think that means he likes staying home?
三次結婚？你認為他喜歡在家？
Means he's one of those guys out there...
他是那種…
prowling around all night, dedicated.
整晚工作的人 很投入
With him and this much heat, you should pass.
有他和警方監視取消搶銀行吧
It's worth the stretch.
值得冒險一試
This guy can hit or miss.
這人可抓到我或是失手
You can't miss once.
你不能出錯
You sure?
你肯定嗎？
I am sure.
肯定
Let's go to the garage.
我們去車房吧
Where are we going?
我們去哪裡？
Where are you going?
你去哪裡？
Out.
外出
What are they on?
他們用什麼頻道？
TAC 9.
九號戰術頻道
They're northbound out LAX on the 405. We got four ground units.
他們在405公路 往機場方向北走
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18. Who have I got?
我是18號機的漢娜·文森特 誰和我合作？
This is JJ. I'm in Air 40.
我是40號機的JJ
Richard Glover's with me. It's on the 105 eastbound...
理查·格羅夫和我一起 車在105公路…
approaching the 110.
東行接近110公路
Revolving tail?
交替追蹤？
I got two units in front, three behind.
兩輛在他前面 三輛在他後面
Have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on-ramp.
要其中一輛在維蒙街接我
Let's go.
走吧
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
我離他百碼嗎？太近還是太遠？
Three hundred yards, center lane.
離他300碼 在中央行車線
How're you doing?
你好嗎？
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
我請你喝咖啡如何？
Yeah, sure. Let's go.
好的 走吧
Follow me.
跟我走
Seven years in Folsom.
你在福爾索姆監獄七年
In the hole for three.
單獨囚禁三年
McNeil before that.
之前在麥考利監獄
McNeil as tough as they say?
那兒是如他們所說的那樣嗎？
You looking to become a penologist?
你是監獄學者嗎？
You looking to go back?
你想再坐牢？
I chased down some crews. Guys just looking to fuck up, get busted back.
我追捕想犯錯被捕的人 拘捕他們
That you?
那你呢？
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
你拘捕的定是飯桶了
I worked all kinds.
我拘捕各式各樣的人
You see me doing liquor store holdups with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
你幻想我身上有刺青行劫酒鋪嗎
I do not.
我看不是
Right.
對
I am never going back.
我不會再坐牢
Then don't take down scores.
那麼便別再行劫
I do what I do best:
我做擅長做的事
I take scores. You do what you do best: Try to stop guys like me.
我行劫 你做擅長的事 阻止我
You never wanted a regular-type life?
你從不想過正常生活？
What is that? Barbecues and ball games?
是怎樣的？燒烤和踢足球嗎？
Yeah.
是的
This regular-type life like your life?
你的生活正常嗎？
My life? No, my life...
我的生活？不 我的生活…
My life's a disaster zone.
一塌糊塗
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
我的繼女情緒深受困擾
because her real father is this large-type asshole.
因她的生父是個大渾蛋
I got a wife.
我有太太…
We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage.
我的婚姻正頻臨破碎邊緣
My third.
第三次婚姻
Because I spend all my time  chasing guys like you around the block.
因我常花時間追捕你這樣的人
That's my life.
那是我的生活
A guy told me one time:
有人曾對我說…
"Don't get attached to anything you can't walk out on in 30 seconds...
若你感到附近有警方監視
"if you feel the heat around the corner."
便不能沾上任何不能脫身的事
If you're on me and you got to move when I move...
你想捉我 我行動時你也行動…
how do you expect to keep a marriage?
你如何能保持婚姻呢？
That's an interesting point.
這說法很有趣
Are you a monk?
你是僧侶嗎？
I have a woman.
我有女伴
What do you tell her?
你怎對她說？
I tell her I'm a salesman.
告訴她我是推銷員
So, if you spot me coming around that corner...
那麼若你見我從街角走來…
you'll just walk out on her?
你會離開她？
Not say good-bye?
不辭而別？
That's the discipline.
這是規矩
That's pretty vacant.
那很空泛
It is what it is.
正是如此
It's that, or we both better go do something else.
不這樣做我們還是另找職業吧
I don't know how to do anything else.
我不懂做別的
Neither do I.
我也不懂
I don't want to either.
我不想
Neither do I.
我也不想
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我不斷重複這夢境
I'm sitting at this big banquet table and...
我坐在偌大的餐宴席上…
all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are there...
我調查的凶案受害人均出席…
and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
他們用黑的眼珠子瞪望我…
because they got eight-ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
因為他們頭部中槍而出血
And there they are, these big balloon people...
這些發脹的屍體在那兒…
because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
因他們被殺兩周後才在床下發現
The neighbors reported the smell...
鄰居報稱有惡臭…
and there they are...
他們均有出席…
all just sitting there.
坐在那兒
What do they say?
他們說什麼？
Nothing.
沒說話
No talk?
沒人說話？
They have nothing to say.
他們無話可說
We just look at each other.
我們彼此望著對方
They look at me...
他們望著我…
and that's it. That's the dream.
就是這樣 夢境是這樣
I have one where I'm drowning.
我做夢自己遇溺
I gotta wake myself up and start breathing or I'll die in my sleep.
我得弄醒自己和呼吸否則會死
Know what that's about?
這象徵什麼？
Having enough time.
有足夠的時間
Enough time...
足夠時間…
to do what you want to do?
做你想做的事？
That's right.
是的
You doing it now?
你現在這樣做？
No, not yet.
還沒有
You know, we're sitting here...
我們坐在這裡…
like a couple of regular fellas.
一如常人
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
彼此做有需要的事
Now that we've been face to face...
現在我們見過面…
if I'm there and I gotta put you away...
若我要在案發現場殺你…
I won't like it.
我會不喜歡
But, I tell you...
但是…
if it's between you...
若在你和…
and some poor bastard whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
給你殺死的人當中作選擇…
brother...
兄弟…
you are going down.
沒命的會是你
There's a flip side to that coin.
我有反面的看法
What if you do got me boxed in...
若你真的使我走投無路…
and I gotta put you down?
而我要殺你呢？
Because no matter what...
因為不管如何…
you won't get in my way.
你也不能阻止我的
We've been face to face, yeah.
是的 我們見過面
But I will not hesitate.
但我會毫不猶疑殺你
Not for a second.
一秒也不遲疑
Maybe that'll happen.
也許會這樣
Or...
或是…
who knows?
誰知道呢？
Maybe we'll never see each other again.
也許我們會永遠不再見
They dumped us.
他們擺脫了我們
What?
什麼？
They dumped us.
他們逃脫了
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
Chris slipped away.
克裡斯逃脫了
He doesn't talk about their scores...
他沒談及買賣的事
so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I just tried.
我無從向馬西阿諾套取資料
What about Cheritto? Same.
克裡托呢？ 也一樣
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
跟蹤收發器放在公共汽車上
They dumped all our surveillance?
他們擺脫我們所有的監視？
Yes, at the same time. 9:00 p.m.
是的 同一時間 晚上九時
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
我半小時前和麥考利喝咖啡
We were on you.
我們在監視你們
Then McCauley drives in to LAX where surveillance can't fly over.
之後麥考利開車進了洛杉磯機場 而我們無法監視
His car's still there. He's gone.
他的車還在 人不見了
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
有誰知道他們在哪兒？
Hear from him?
他有聯絡嗎？
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more. Where's this guy?
沒有 這令我不安 他在哪兒？
This guy...
這人…
we put him on.
我們雇用他
Says he knows McCauley.
他說認識麥考利
Who are you?
你是誰？
Waingro.
韋恩格羅
My name's Waingro.
我叫韋恩格羅
I've been living in this office. How well do you know him?
我等他電話 你很熟識他嗎？
We took some major scores together.
我們一起做過不少大買賣
Why haven't I heard from him?
他為何沒找我？
He's probably busy right now.
他可能忙著
But he's real thorough.
但他行事很徹底
He ain't going to forget about you.
他不會忘記你的
That's reassuring.
那令人很安心
I got some moves I could make here.
我可在這兒出了力
Probably be a big help to you.
可能對你會很有幫助
You recognize the grill man?
認得那烤肉的人嗎？
No.
不認識
Folsom.
福爾索姆監獄
D-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
D座的 和杜比·拉什同一囚室
I ain't got my break yet.
我還沒有休息
Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
思科和潘丘沒上班
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
扔垃圾 到餐廳後拖地
Take your break later.
稍後才休息
Piece of shit.
人渣
Pick up!
送出去吧
Where the hell is he?
他在哪兒？
I want to check the slot for the work car.
我查看車場看車是否仍在那兒
So did I.
我也想
Hang on.
等一等
Use the land line. Call me at 103-7206.
用普通電話打來 103-7206
Where are you?
你在哪兒？
There's cops all over me, man, like a cheap suit.
到處有員警監視我
I can't dump them.
我無法擺脫他們
They know you see them?
他們知道你看見他們
They're doing parallels.
他們平行緊貼我
I can try to dump them again.
我可試著擺脫他們
How are we going to know if you did?
我怎知道你是否擺脫了？
If not, you'll draw them to us.
你會引他們來找我們
Go to Ventura.
到文圖拉去
Pull them out of here.
讓他們離開那裡
I'm sorry. Last thing I wanted to do was let you down.
對不起 我不想讓你失望的
Pick up.
送出去
Neil, man. What's up?
尼爾 你好嗎？
What's up?
你好嗎？
What are you doing here?
你在這兒做什麼？
I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners on the radio.
我在找能夠應付警方無線電追蹤的司機
Right now, today.
現在便要
You remember the drill?
你還記得嗎？
Yeah, sure.
記得
You cool?
你可信任嗎？
You know I'm cool.
你知我可信任
One answer: yes or no. Right now.
你現在便答我 肯或不肯
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
好的 去它的 我答應
Out back in five.
五分鐘後到後面
What's burning?
是什麼燒焦了？
What is this?
是什麼事？
Where do you think you're going?
你去哪裡？
Don't move! Put your hands in the air!
別動！舉起手來！
Hands up!
舉手！
Put them up! Now!
快點舉起來！
Get on your knees!
跪下！
The keys!
給我鑰匙
Get on your knees!
跪下！
Get over there!
過去那邊！
Turn around!
轉身！
Put your hands behind you!
把手放在背後！
Get down!
躺下！
Stay down!
別動
Get down!
趴下！
Down! The keys! The keys!
拿鎖匙來！
Stay down!
別動
We want to hurt no one. We want the bank's money, not your money.
我們不想傷人 只要銀行的錢
Your money is insured by the government. You won't lose a dime.
你們不會損失 政府購了保險
Think of your families.
想想你的家人
Don't risk your life. Don't be a hero.
別冒生命危險
I want you to sit on the floor, put your hands on your head. Anybody feels sick...
你們坐在地上手放頭上 不舒服
anybody got heart trouble, lean against the wall.
或心臟有事 便靠在牆上
The key.
給我鎖匙
What key?
什麼鎖匙？
Sit down and stay down!
都別動
Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
坐下 別動 讓傷口淌血吧
Get down. Down, down, down.
趴下
Put your heads down!
低下頭！
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
你調查尼爾·麥考利的案？
This C.I., Hugh Benny, called in about a bank.
線人修·班尼說關於搶銀行
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
早上十一時半遠東國家銀行！
I want a block at Figueroa and Fifth...
在第五街交界設路障…
and I want a block northbound Flower at Sixth.
花街及第六界北行也設路障
They're already coming out.
他們出來了
We gotta take them in the car.
要在車上捉他們
Wait till they are all in.
等他們全上車後才動手
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
要俐落的殺他們 別傷及無辜
Police! Move!
員警！走開！
Move. Move. Get down.
閃開閃開
Move it. Down, down.
走開！趴下
We did it!
我們成功了！
Move!
走開！
Get down!
趴下
Get in the car!
開車！
Go! Go!
走！
Go!
走
Come on!
振作點
Get down!
伏下
All the way down! Get down! Now!
緊趴在地上！快趴下！
Come here.
過來
I got you.
我來抱你
Tragedy in the neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
今天發生慘劇銀行劫案禍延街上
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest.
克勞迪婭·紐曼現時在現場作最新報導
This afternoon, a neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
今天下午搶銀行不遂使這兒很可怕
With the streets full of shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
街上滿是行人 警方和劫匪…
Excuse me, bartender.
打擾了 酒保
Our top story tonight: Robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
新聞提要：搶劫 追逐 死亡
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
銀行劫案震動洛杉磯地區…
that ended in homicide and terror.
最後以兇殺及恐怖活動告終
Michael Cheritto...
邁克爾·克裡托…
one of four men involved in the foiled robbery, died at the scene.
是四名劫匪之一 在現場死去
Also fatally wounded: another suspect, Donald Breedan, who died of gunshot wounds...
另一涉案嫌疑人 唐納德·布裡丹 死於槍傷…
during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
當時警方和疑匪正激烈駁火
All right, hold him.
好了 按著他
It's all right.
沒事的
So?
怎樣？
He's got blood loss and shock.
他失血和受驚
I'll give you quarter-grain bottles of morphine for the pain.
我給你最少量的嗎啡止痛
Bottom line?
很重嗎
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good.
主要是組織受損 那是好事
His clavicle's fractured. Can you rest?
他的鎖骨折斷 可讓他休息嗎？
Six, seven hours.
6、7小時
That's it? That's it.
不能多留？是的
Take off your shirt.
脫下襯衣
What?
什麼？
Take off your shirt.
脫下襯衣
My daughter gave it to me.
這是我女兒給我的
I don't give a shit. Take it off.
我不管 脫下來
Listen to me.
聽著
Nate's going to pick you up. He's going to take you to his place.
內特會接你 送你到他家中
Where's Charlene?
沙琳呢？
We gotta go. We're on the 6:00 news. We gotta get out of here.
新聞播銀行的事 我們要離去
I'm not going without her.
沒有她我不走
Think about that.
你考慮一下
I will meet you at Nate's.
在內特那兒見
Where are you going?
你去哪兒？
To find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
查探逃走路線是否給洩露了
Who did it?
是誰告密的？
Who wasn't there?
有誰沒參加？
Trejo.
特喬
See you at Nate's.
在內特家見
You still want me?
你仍想要我嗎？
You come down here right now and get me. Dominick and me.
你來這裡接我和多明尼克吧
Okay, baby.
好的 寶貝
I'll be there in two hours.
我兩小時後到
All right.
好吧
Goddamn you, Chris.
你該死 克裡斯
Goddamn you.
你該死
You're on a plane to Los Angeles.
你坐飛機往洛杉磯
Right.
好的
Why did you do it? What happened?
你為何這樣做？怎麼回事？
They made me. Who?
他們逼我 誰？
Where's Anna?
安娜呢？
She's dead.
她死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
邁克爾和代替你的布裡丹也死了
Who did it?
誰逼你的？
誰？
They had Anna, man.
他們威脅安娜
Who?
是誰？
Waingro.
韋恩格羅
On his own?
他一個人？
For someone. Who?
替人賣命 誰
The other he worked for.
他替別人工作…
Van Zant.
範·贊特
Van Zant?
範·贊特？
Are you sure?
你肯定嗎？
Van Zant.
範·贊特
Did you tell them how we're getting out?
你有說出我們怎樣逃走嗎？
I don't think so.
我想沒有
Come on.
說吧
I don't remember.
我不記得
I'll call a medic.
我通知救護員
I'm not going to make it.
我無法活下去的
I can't feel nothing.
我全無感覺
My Anna's gone.
我的安娜死了
She's gone.
她死了
Don't leave me like this.
別這樣扔下我
Please, homes.
求求你 送我回家
Don't leave me like this.
別這樣扔下我
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
你用無線電話嗎？用普通電話
It's a new one.
這是新的電話
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
他住在艾西諾區山景台
10725.
10725號
Chris?
克裡斯呢？
He's with me, my place.
他和我一起在我家中
Next, Waingro, okay?
跟著查出韋恩格羅在哪兒
You got the time?
你有時間嗎？
I'll make time.
我會抽空的
And I need a new out.
我要新的逃走路線
Is it blown?
已經暴露了？
How can I trust it?
我怎能信任呢？
You got it.
好的
Stay healthy.
保住性命
Charlene Shiherlis.
沙琳·謝裡斯
Drucker's got a safe house  in Venice to stash her in.
德魯克在威尼斯區有地方收藏她
Neil's transportation.
尼爾的逃走方法
Get on the phone. Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
正有人替他安排一切
You don't believe he already had a plan?
你不是認為他已有計劃吧？
Sure. Now he needs another.
他需要另一個計畫
Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
今天之後你還相信逃走計畫嗎？
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
這告密的人 哪兒找到他的？
He's a C.I. for a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
他是機密線人通報搶銀行線索
On Neil McCauley.
說說麥考利吧
How much time we got?
還有多少時間？
Eight, ten hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone, bye-bye.
他有8至10小時安排新逃走路線
You ratted McCauley to us! How'd you know?
你向我們告發麥考利！你怎知道？
Who told you?
誰告訴你的？
Who told you, rat motherfucker?
是誰告訴你的？混蛋
Who?
是誰？
Waingro, where is he?
韋恩格羅在哪兒？
Where?
在哪兒？
How would I know?
我怎知道？
Well...
好的
what do we have here?
這兒有些什麼？
This pretty?
這兒漂亮嗎？
漂亮嗎？
You piece of shit.
你這小人
Told me you wanted out from under. You're scared, right?
你告訴我想脫離目前困境
You want out? This is out.
你想脫身嗎？這是出路
Yeah, what's your end? I don't need no stupid broad.
你有何得益？我不需要笨女人
How'd I get into this?
我怎會牽涉此事的？
Easy.
別衝動
You heard me. She had a rough ride.
你聽到的 她生活坎坷
Fix her a drink.
給她喝杯酒
Look in the cabinet above the sink.
到櫥櫃看看
Fuck her.
去她的
You better get in there and stay in there.
你最好進去和不要出來
Lookie here.
聽著
My name is Sgt. Drucker, LAPD Homicide.
我是洛杉磯警局德魯克警官
You want to put Dominick in the bedroom?
要送多明尼克進睡房嗎？
He stays with me.
他和我一起
So, what now?
那麼 現在怎辦？
He's right.
他說的對
You want out? This is out.
你想脫身？這是出路
You believe you have to betray Chris?
你認為你要出賣克裡斯？
No shit.
正是
That's right. You would have to.
對 你最好這樣做
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
若你不出賣克裡斯 多明尼克會是受害人
'Cause he'll be an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
你入獄時他會是孤兒
'cause you got no parents to take him. So he ends up raised in foster homes...
沒有父母照顧 他會被送進收養所…
juvenile facilities.
青少年中心
Then he steals a car.
之後他會偷車
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
然後入獄學會做真正的罪犯
Fucked for life.
毀了一生
You know what happens, because you've been there.
你是過來人 知道會有何下場
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life. But Chris did.
多明尼克沒機會選擇生活但克裡斯有
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
若供出克裡斯 你會沒有案底
You can do it...
你可以的…
for your kid, so you can raise him.
為孩子而這樣做你可撫養他
What else are you selling?
還有什麼條件？
All kinds of shit.
各種的東西
But I don't have to sell this, you know it. This kind of shit here sells itself.
但我不用說服你因為我是對的
Here's an update.
最新消息
Drucker's on Line 2.
德魯克在二線
Hold on for a second.
等一等
Drucker's on the other line.
德魯克在另一電話線
Conference him in.
三人通話吧
Go ahead.
說吧
Vincent, it's me.
文森特 是我
One answer. What's it going to be?
你的答覆是怎樣？
We're set here. She'll make the call.
我們準備好 她會打電話
That's good. Here's the deal.
好的 情況是這樣
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life...
修·班尼已改過自新…
and become a born-again good citizen.
成為洗心革面的好市民
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
叫韋恩格羅的人向我們出賣尼爾
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew, then went to work for a money launderer:
韋恩格羅曾是他手下 後替洗錢人工作
Van Zant.
他叫範·贊特
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak...
現時正派人住範·贊特家中…
because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
因為他今晚較早前被殺
If Neil goes after anybody else, it's going to be Waingro.
尼爾要對付的人會是韋恩格羅
Waingro just got himself a suite at the Airport Marquis...
韋恩格羅正入住侯爵機場酒店套房…
under the name Jamieson.
並化名傑米森
He's there now. I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
他到了 我要你把這消息告訴…
assignment officers and snitches in County.
週邊 指派警員及線人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street. Deploy a team at the hotel...
任何把消息外泄的人 部署一個小組到酒店
and personally check their coms every 30 minutes.
並每隔半小時收聽無線電
Because maybe Neil will go for him.
也許尼爾會殺他
How're you feeling?
你感到怎樣？
Banged up, but I'll live.
沒問題 我會好的
He's here.
他仍在
Neil is still here.
尼爾還沒走
I can feel it.
我可感覺到
For how long?
會留多久？
Seven, eight hours, max.
最多七八個小時
What did you do?
你做過什麼？
That was you?
是你做的？
I don't sell metal.
我不是賣金屬的
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
計畫本順利但現在出了麻煩
We gotta go together.
我們要一起走
Those other people were with you?
那些人和你一起？
My friend, Michael...
我的朋友邁克爾…
he knew the risks.
他知道所冒的險
When it rains, you get wet.
身處險境便要冒生命危險
Get packed. Let's go.
收拾東西 走吧
Why did you do this to me?
你為何這樣對我？
It'll be all right.
不會有事的
Do you understand?
明白嗎？
It's going to be all right.
不會有事的
There's a Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
這位址D層18單位有一汽車
Here's some cash.
這兒有現金
When is it over?
此事何時結束？
Twenty-two hours from now.
22小時後
Then we get out of here clean. When will you let me leave?
你何時會讓我離去
Go now.
不知道
You want out? There's the door.
門在那邊
Will you let me leave later?
你稍後會讓我離去嗎？
It will be different.
情況會不同
Do you even understand?
你不明白？
It's ready.
準備好了
This is my friend Ralph.
這是我的朋友拉爾夫
You didn't tell me you were...
你沒說你已然…
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Where's Lauren?
勞倫呢？
She's at Lisa-Beth's.
她在麗莎貝絲家中
This has nothing to do with me. I'm sorry.
此事和我無關 對不起
What for?
你對不起誰？
Sit down.
坐下
Don't you get angry?
你不生氣嗎？
I'm angry.
我生氣
I'm very angry, Ralph.
我很生氣 拉爾夫
You can ball my wife if she wants you to.
若她想你幹她你可幹我太太
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
你可躺在她的沙發上
In her ex-husband's...
在她前夫的…
dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house...
高科技後現代主義的荒謬家中
if you want to.
若你想的話
But you do not get to watch...
但你不能看…
my fucking...
我該死的
television set!
電視機
For God's sake.
天啊
Put the television set down.
把電視機放下
I never cheated on you, bitch. Maybe you should have.
我沒對你不忠 也許你應該
I should have? You're a party to this.
我應該嗎？
I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
我要拉爾夫幹你因為這使我開心
Our situation is absurd.
我們的處境荒謬
Ah Look. May be
其實我可以
Shut up, Ralph! Sit down!
住口 拉爾夫！坐下！
Why is it that I have to figure things out and explain them to you?
我為何要向你解釋事情
I say what I mean, and I do what I say.
我的說話是認為的也言出必行
How admirable.
多麼可敬
You bet. Except none of it's about us.
可是沒什麼是和我們有關的
No.
是的
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac but...
我要是抽大麻或服興奮劑迷糊了
you walk through our life dead.
但你在我們的生活中猶如死了
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
我要自貶找拉爾夫終斷我們關係
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
護照、旅行支票、信用卡
The plane...
這飛機…
charter terminal, LAX, Hangar 17.
在洛杉磯機場包機站十七號機庫
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
確定密碼是1011山嶺
Touches down...
飛機會降落…
holds for you five minutes, then splits.
等你五分鐘然後便起飛
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
飛機會通過航空局檢查等手續
Where's Chris?
克裡斯呢？
He's gone.
他走了
What?
什麼？
Said he's going on his own. Went to find Charlene.
他說去找沙琳 他走了
Did you bring him here? Yeah, I did.
你帶他來這兒了？是的
What happened?
怎麼回事？
It's a free country.
這是個自由國家
Check in with me at 9:00...
晚上九點聯絡我…
everything is still cool.
確保一切妥當
All right.
好的
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
我已不知自己在做什麼？
I know life is short.
我知道生命短促
Whatever time you get is luck.
能活多久是運氣
You want to walk?
你想終斷這段關係？
You walk right now...
你現在離去…
all on your own.
是自願的…
On your own you choose to come with me.
你自願選擇跟我走
All I know is...
我只知道…
there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
我無謂再到任何地方去
if it's going to be alone...
若我會獨自一人…
without you.
沒有你在身邊
I got a live one.
我找到一個
I'll hold.
我等著
Show yourself.
讓他看見你
Do it. Shut up!
去啊 住口！
Now, just one second at the window...
只需在窗前站一秒
and it's all over.
此事便會了結
Hey, man...
朋友…
you know any place to rent around here?
你知這附近有地方租嗎？
The grocer has got cards on the wall.
雜貨店牆上有招租告示
It's not him.
不是他
It's not Chris.
不是克裡斯
Unit 2, this is Command.
這裡是指揮部
Take him at the street.
攔住他
Check him out.
查明他的身份
He's John Peterson.
他叫約翰·彼得森
Valid ID. Car's registered to...
有效的身份證 車輛登記人是…
Bukowski, Gene.
布考斯基 基恩
Ran it to DMV.
向運輸署查核過
It's clean.
沒有不妥
Let him go.
讓他走
Roger.
知道
Thank you. Have a good evening.
謝謝 晚安
It's no-go.
不是他
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait?
我們等待的時候你想喝咖啡嗎？
Yeah, that would be nice.
那會很不錯
What do you got?
你有什麼消息？
Nothing's happening.
沒事發生
Hello, it's Vincent.
我是文森特
What do you got?
有何動靜？
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice.
沒有 韋恩格羅去拿冰塊
That's it.
就這樣
You know what?
你知道嗎？
Neil is gone.
尼爾走了
Flying like a bird.
像鳥兒般飛走
How do you know?
你怎知道？
We still got bait!
我們仍然有誘餌
Maybe some time! What do we got?
也許仍有時間
What do we got?
我們有什麼？
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
旅途愉快 雜種
You were good.
你很了得
I'm going to the hotel.
我到酒店去
I'm going to take a shower...
我會洗澡
and I'm going to sleep for a month.
然後睡個昏天暗地
Here.
來
Come on.
醒來吧
Shit.
見鬼
Motherfucking waste.
浪費生命
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day.
渾蛋才應該自毀
Not you, baby.
不是你 寶貝
Not you.
你不會的
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren.
她會在哪兒？她叫勞倫
Lauren Gustafson, and she's supposed to be here.
勞倫·古斯塔夫森 她該在這兒的
I need somebody to help...
我要人幫忙…
I got you.
我抱著你
You'll be all right, I swear. It's okay, baby.
你會沒事的 會沒事的
Let's get a doctor!
找醫生來！
Let's go! A doctor here!
我要醫生！
There's your mama. Let's just calm down.
冷靜下來
Is she on any drugs? I'm calm. No.
她服用藥物嗎？
Get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
找精神創傷及血管醫生來
I think she cut both arteries. I could hardly feel her pulse.
她割斷兩條動脈她沒有脈搏
Her pressure's down.
她的血壓下降
So is her respiration. You have to intubate her.
要給她插管
It's ready.
準備好了
When's the last time anybody saw her?
最後一次見她時是什麼時候？
I don't know.
我不知道
Where did you find her?
你在哪兒找到她？
The bathtub.
浴缸
Give her large-bore normal saline.
給她注射大針管的鹽水
Keep pressure on those bleeders.
緊按出血的血管
Give me two units, O-negative. Let's type and cross her for six.
兩公升O型血查出她血型和輸血
Where is Respiratory? We need more help. Get them down now.
呼吸科專家呢？我們需要幫忙
Let's have X-ray ready for post-intubation chest X-ray.
準備插管後照X光
Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room.
令媛已做過手術及在療養室
Her vital signs are stable.
她情況穩定
The surgeon will speak to you in a few moments.
醫生很快會跟你說
She's okay?
她沒事吧？
She's doing good.
她很好
She'll be okay.
她會沒事的
She's going to be okay.
她不會有事
Oh, my baby. Why did she do this to herself?
我的女兒 她為何這樣對自己？
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
看她把自己怎麼了
It's all right. It's going to be all right.
沒事的 不會有事的
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
我在這兒 不會到別處去
Do you understand? I ain't going anywhere.
明白嗎？我不會到別處去
It's me.
是我
Plane's in the air now. You're right on time.
飛機已在半空 你準時離去
I still can't find a driver...
仍找不到
so that's in the trust.
可以信任的司機
One other thing...
還有一事…
I gotta tell you.
我得告訴你
The guy you want is in the Marquis under Jamieson, if you still give a shit...
你找的人在候爵酒店化名傑米森
which I figured you wouldn't.
我看你不想找他吧
You figured right.
你說的對
So, so long, brother.
再見 兄弟
You take it easy.
保重了
You're home free.
你不用擔心什麼
Take it easy.
保重
What is it?
怎麼了？
Nothing.
沒什麼
Home free.
了無牽掛
I gotta take care of something.
我得解決一些事情
Is there time?
有時間嗎？
There's time.
有的
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
我很快回來 讓車子開動吧
Registration.
入住登記
This is room service.
房間餐飲部
A Jamieson ordered a BLT, and they screwed up his room number. What is it?
傑米森要了食物但房號弄錯了
They're always doing that. I know.
經常會弄錯 是啊
1735.
1735號房
Thank you.
謝謝
Your attention, please.
請注意
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
現時響起火警警報
Do not panic.
不用驚慌
Do not take the elevators.
不要乘坐電梯
I'm staying here.
我留在這兒
I'll check the stairs. If there's smoke, I'll pull you out.
我查看樓梯若有煙便會要你走
What about her dad? Should I call him?
我該通知她父親嗎？
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
他在內華達山脈某處
And she chose you.
她選上你
She picked your place.
選你的房間自殺
It's not right, what happened to her.
這樣做是不對的
No, it's not.
是的
Is there any way that...
是否有辦法…
it could work out between us?
可克服我們間的問題？
I wish I could say yes, you know.
我希望說有 你知道
But...
可是…
in the end...
到最後…
It's like you said:
就像你說的…
All I am...
我沉迷於…
is what I'm going after.
追捕我的罪犯
I'm not what you want, Justine.
我不是你想要的人 賈斯汀
Go on, if you have to.
若你要走便走吧
I'll stay.
我會留下
I'm okay. I can handle this.
我沒事 我可應付
Just be careful.
你保重
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
給我電話讓我知道你沒事
Okay?
好嗎？
Security. There's a fire on three.
酒店保安 發生火警
We have to evacuate all floors.
各樓層的人均要疏散
I can't leave here.
我不能離去
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, brother?
我們何不先談一下？
He's here on 17.
他在十七樓
Look at me.
望著我
Look at me!
望著我！
LAPD! Don't move!
洛杉磯員警！別動！
Put your hands on your head!
手放在頭上！
Switch me to TAC 5.
將我轉到五號頻道
Casals...
卡薩爾斯…
JJ...
Drucker, JJ...
德魯克 JJ
I'm in the lobby level by the stairwell.
我在大堂接近樓梯井
What have you got?
有什麼事？
Teams are moving up the other  elevators to the 17th floor.
有人乘另一電梯往十七樓
Elevators are all out of commission because of the fire alarm.
因火警警鐘響起升降機不能用
Fine. 10-4.
好的 收到
Let me have that shotgun.
把槍給我
Told you I'm never going back.
早說過我不會回監獄的
Yeah.
是的